LIVE FROM EL PASO.
Gabriel Iglesias: I'm Not Fat... I'm Fluffy is a comedy,
tv movie film directed by Manny Rodriguez.
Gabriel Iglesias entertains a packed house at El Paso's
Theatre in this Comedy Central special.
For I'm Not Fat, I'm Fluffy, the comedian reaches new heights of hilarity,
providing eerily perfect imitations and tales too tall not to be true.
He also adds a new step to his five levels of fatness, and the sixth
level is sure to leave audiences rolling in the aisles.
Himself, played by Gabriel Iglesias.
Gabriel Jesús Iglesias (born July 15, 1976), nicknamed Fluffy,
is an American stand-up comedian and actor.
He has produced a number of stand-up specials for television outlets such
as Comedy Central and Netflix, including I'm Not Fat...
I'm Fluffy, and Hot and Fluffy.
As an actor, he has appeared in numerous live-action and animated TV
shows and films, including starring in the sitcom Mr.
Iglesias on Netflix, playing Tobias in the 2012 movie Magic Mike and its 2015 sequel,
and providing the voice of Speedy Gonzales in Space Jam: A New Legacy.
He was also the host of the shows Stand Up Revolution on Comedy
Central and Fluffy's Food Adventures on Fuse.
In 2018, Iglesias was one of the top 10 highest paid comedians in the world.
The tone is lighthearted.